VARSHA MESHRAM

SAPFICO

Linkedin

SUMMARY

Experienced finance professional with a strong background in general ledger basic accounting and banking reconciliation. Ability to multitask and excel in office administration. Proficient in MS Excel and effective communication skills. working in a team-based environment

CONTACT

Phone: 9970609032

Email: varsh55asl@gmail.com Address: Balaghat Madhya Pradesh

SKILLS

- SAP FICO ECC 6,
- SAPS/4HANA
- Accounts Payable (AP)
- Accounts Receivable (AR)
- SAP ERP
- SAP FI/CO Configuration
- Xero Software
- Microsoft excel
- Accounting
- Bank Reconciliation
- General Ledgers
- Bookkeeping
- Financial Accounting

Soft Skills

- Good attitude and learning Desire
- Good client-handling skills
- Able to manage customers independently
- Ready to relocate to any location

EDUCATION

Masters in Business Administration

Finance and Marketing

RTMNU Nagpur University 2010-2012

Bachelor of Science

RDVV JABALPUR UNIVERSITY 2006-2009

LANGUAGES

- Hindi Native
- English Proficient
- Marathi Beginner

EXPERIENCE

Accountant

Samriddhi Construction from May 2023

- Basic accounting to ensure accurate
 Transaction and classification of financial transactions, facilitating smooth and error-free financial operations.
- Bank and cash reconciliations, ensuring that discrepancies are promptly identified and resolved, leading to enhanced financial transparency.

Accountant

Vaibhav finance- January 2019-march 2023

- Handling Back office Administration
- Basic Accounting
- General ledger,
- Bank Reconciliation
- office administration
- Sales and Promotion
- Communication

Account Officer

Shriram chits (m) ltd - Dec2012 -April 2014

- Handling Back Office Administration
- Handling Cash Flow Management
- Bank Reconciliation
- Cash Reconciliation
- MIS-CMS Report
- Handling Gold Loan Accounting
- Handling Product Promotion, Event Management & Product Training.
- Selling Chit Fund products through the Agency Channel as well as the Executive Team.
- Continuous follow-ups with clients of the Agents.
- Creating awareness among customers about various products offered by the company.
- Need analysis of customers and providing suitable products.